{
    "id": "569952bf27154411a723dbcebc1087cd",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "‘I didn’t pass the test.’ ‘…………………………. did I.’",
            "description": "After a negative statement, we can add another negative statement to it with neither or nor. ",
            "answers": [
                "Either",
                "Neither",
                "Nor"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She is …………………………. beautiful.",
            "description": "Too shows unwanted extremes. ",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "so much"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am …………………………… happy.",
            "description": "We do not use so much to modify adjectives and adverbs.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "so much"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Start at once, …………………………… you do not miss the train.",
            "description": "Either so that or in order that cannot be used here.",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "so as to",
                "in order that",
                "in order to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I waited for ………………………… two hours but he didn’t come.",
            "description": "We can use another with plural expressions of quantity.",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "another",
                "an other"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Buses leave ………………………….. ten minutes.",
            "description": "Every can be used before plural expressions in measurements of frequency.",
            "answers": [
                "every",
                "all",
                "each"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My ……………………………… been stolen.",
            "description": "Baggage does not have a plural form. ",
            "answers": [
                "baggage have",
                "baggage has",
                "baggages have"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Alice and James ……………………………. agreed to come.",
            "description": "When two singular nouns are connected by and, the verb should be plural. ",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He sings as well as ………………………… the guitar.",
            "description": "He sings as well as playing the guitar means 'He not only plays the guitar, but also sings.'",
            "answers": [
                "plays",
                "playing",
                "play"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The more he earns, the …………………………. he spends.",
            "description": "Less is the comparative form of little. The comparative is used in both clauses in this structure. ",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "lesser",
                "little"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It is cruel …………………………… animals in that way.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to treat",
                "for treating",
                "to treating"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I was …………………………. tired that I couldn’t walk any further.",
            "description": "Note the pattern so...that...",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "very",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}